question_data =[
    {
        "type": "boolean",
        "difficulty": "easy",
        "category": "Geography",
        "question": "San Marino is the only country completely surrounded by another country.",
        "correct_answer": "False",
        "incorrect_answers": ["True"]
    },
    {
        "type": "boolean",
        "difficulty": "easy",
        "category": "Geography",
        "question": "There are no deserts in Europe.",
        "correct_answer": "True",
        "incorrect_answers": [
            "False"
        ]
    },
    {
        "type": "boolean",
        "difficulty": "easy",
        "category": "Geography",
        "question": "Hungary is the only country in the world beginning with H.",
        "correct_answer": "False",
        "incorrect_answers": [
            "True"
        ]
    },
    {
        "type": "boolean",
        "difficulty": "easy",
        "category": "Geography",
        "question": "Tokyo is the capital of Japan.",
        "correct_answer": "True",
        "incorrect_answers": [
            "False"
        ]
    },
    {
        "type": "boolean",
        "difficulty": "easy",
        "category": "Geography",
        "question": "There is a city called Rome in every continent on Earth.",
        "correct_answer": "False",
        "incorrect_answers": [
            "True"
        ]
    },
    {
        "type": "boolean",
        "difficulty": "easy",
        "category": "Geography",
        "question": "There is an island in Japan called \u014ckunoshima, A.K.A. \"Rabbit Island\", so named because of it's huge population of rabbits.",
        "correct_answer": "True",
        "incorrect_answers": [
            "False"
        ]
    },
    {
        "type": "boolean",
        "difficulty": "easy",
        "category": "Geography",
        "question": "The Republic of Malta is the smallest microstate worldwide.",
        "correct_answer": "False",
        "incorrect_answers": [
            "True"
        ]
    },
    {
        "type": "boolean",
        "difficulty": "easy",
        "category": "Geography",
        "question": "Toronto is the capital city of the North American country of Canada.",
        "correct_answer": "False",
        "incorrect_answers": [
            "True"
        ]
    },
    {
        "type": "boolean",
        "difficulty": "easy",
        "category": "Geography",
        "question": "Greenland is covered with grass and Iceland covered with ice.",
        "correct_answer": "False",
        "incorrect_answers": [
            "True"
        ]
    },
    {
        "type": "boolean",
        "difficulty": "easy",
        "category": "Geography",
        "question": "Nova Scotia is on the east coast of Canada.",
        "correct_answer": "True",
        "incorrect_answers": [
            "False"
        ]
    }
]